Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trial, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
A young Yami was out training when he received a request to protect a village from a group of bandit mages.
But before he knew it, he found himself outnumbered and surrounded.
And during that fateful fight...
Yami, I believe your name was. Watch my back if you wouldn't mind.
Yami met William Von Gens, who was on his own mission nearby.
I intend to become the captain of the Magic Knight Squad. Then it's a contest. Let's see who gets there first.
After all that, a whole bunch of stuff happened. Years went by. Old Julius was crowned as the Wizard King.
And as for me and my new pal Goldiguts, both of us ended up getting promoted to vice-captain of the Grey Deer.
Then one day...
Ah, yes. It's wonderful to see you. How are things?
Let's skip the small talk if you don't mind. I agree.
By the way, William, I was happy to hear about your excellent work investigating the dungeon that was recently discovered.
Oh, that was nothing, sir.
Don't be so modest. You valiantly used your magic to rescue your trapped squadmates.
Boy, I wish I could have seen that!
Ah, and such a noble effort is obviously worthy of a star. Nice work.
I'm honored. Thank you, Your Majesty.
And apparently you fought like a man possessed during the treacherous battle to defend the village of Kuka.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but I believe I heard you slice the enemy's giant stone magic warrior in two.
Oh, come on. That was amazing. And I'm gonna get a star for my heroics too, right?
Of course! Your captain must be beaming with pride right now.
Wizard King, it's time, sir.
Right, I almost forgot. I appreciate you coming all this way when you're so busy, but…
But…
It would appear that I have a new assignment lined up for you to do.
Bandits?
Indeed. They've been making mischief all over. Do you think you could take care of them for us?
Certainly. We are magic knights, after all. We are here to serve the people of the Clover Kingdom. So we'll go.
And happily. However…
Why are you sending us and only us?
Well, we have reason to believe that these bandits may be receiving help from someone who's part of the magic knights.
Ah, so it'll take a little finesse.
Hmm. This isn't just some ordinary band of miscreants. From what we've observed, we understand these people are considerably powerful,
their leadership is unusually strong, and they're currently in possession of ancient magic items. Plus…
It seems they may have absconded with some magic artifacts that were found in the dungeons.
So you came to us. Well, I guess that makes sense.
If you'd addressed the magic knights as a whole, someone within the ranks could have disposed of evidence that might reveal the truth. That's why we need to handle it discreetly.
That about covers it.
Just one thing though, Julius. What are you gonna do if it turns out William and I were the big traitors all along? We would probably turn a blind eye to those bandits, right?
Indeed, that would be a problem. But then… I like to believe I know you fellows fairly well. Even from the days before you became members of the magic knights. So I'm assuming it's safe to trust you. Although if you do decide to betray me, I guess that's the way life goes.
Huh. You got a strange outlook on life, Julius.
Marks, would you please do the honors?
Yes, sir.
The towns and villages that have been attacked by the bandits are indicated here.
Oh, I see. They're all over the place. They must not want us to figure out which area they're gonna go after next. Huh.
We've sent word to local magic knight squads telling them to be extra vigilant. But even that bit of information could be subject to leaks.
They tend to focus on the places with weaker defenses.
So basically, we're gonna have to guess at what their next target will be and hope we get it right. And that will not be an easy task.
No, I think it will be. Huh?
We can start by ruling out all the spots that have already been hit. The places that are most at risk would be where treasure has recently been discovered. Or anywhere a harvest is about to take place. Especially a large one.
That's real nice detective work, but we're still looking at one or two dozen here.
We can exclude any location that's near a place they've already attacked as well. And they'll most likely avoid any areas that are on high alert.
Maybe, but...
But that's too many for just the two of us to manage. I'm well aware. So, here and here. This village as well. Could you dispatch some squads to these three areas to watch for bandits?
What for? If word gets out, it'll be all for nothing anyway, you know?
That's brilliant. And assuming the information does get leaked, we can simply use it to our advantage.
Correct. It's safe to assume the bandits will avoid the regions where Magic Knights are. They're probably going to appear where they believe no one will be waiting for them.
Yeah, obviously I knew that. I was just making sure you knew it too, that's all.
Anyway, it looks like we've narrowed it down to one of two spots. The town of Aimaya or Zokudani Village.
Kikiiki, kiki, kibibimeno koto. W**ła, wa, wa, wa wa Joel kano ygada data kafawa bwoバ bwokokok
Thank you.
Exactly. If the bandits show up in Sokodani looking for that treasure, then they would have received their intel far too quickly. In which case there's no doubt we have a traitor in our midst.
Got it. How's I, Maya?
Yeah.
It seems to be all clear as well. They're done reaping and now they're preparing for their harvest festival. It's sure to be a plentiful crop this year.
Well, that'll give the bandits something to steal.
Look, just so we're on the same page. No matter which of us sees the thieves first, we shouldn't do it alone. We should contact each other and wait to attack until we're both present. Agreed?
Yeah, yeah. But you better not pull a fast one on me and try and get all the stars for yourself.
I'd never. Anyway, I'll let you know if I notice any movement.
Guess it's that time.
Hey, Mass Boy. You're on the move. You there? Hey!
The hell? It was working fine earlier.
There's something about this key. Are those guys blocking the flow of mana somehow?
They gotta be doing something to break up our lines of communication.
These are not your run-of-the-mill bandits.
That means there is a traitor. And we just have to figure out who.
Looks like about 30 of them. No more than that. I'm gonna say it's around 50.
50. No matter which of us sees the thieves first, we shouldn't do it alone. We should contact each other.
Well, we can't contact each other, so I'm moving on to plan B.
Sorry, I'm going solo.
Stop them before they get there.
Dark Cloak.
Black Blade!
Who's back there?
Spread out! We've been spotted!
Who is this guy?
A magic knight? You've got guts fighting us all alone.
Yeah, big mistake, pal.
Whatever. Dark magic. Dark Cloak.
Lightless Flash!
Yeah!
I got about half of them.
You must be the boss man.
Wait, I think I know you.
That's odd. You don't look like a magic knight.
Hey, I recognize you.
Yeah, you're gonna have to remind me.
Years ago, you were the one who interfered with our attack on that pathetic village.
Who knew I'd get to settle a score here?
I don't follow.
Oh, that was you.
I remember now.
He looks flashy, but he actually doesn't have a whole lot of magic power to speak of.
That wand he's got's another story, though.
I bet you anything it's a priceless treasure that was dug up in one of those dungeons.
I've changed quite a bit since the last time we fought.
Who cares?
I'm more interested in who gave you that wand.
You want to find out, you'll have to beat me first.
It's over!
That turned out to be a whole lot of nothing.
Now.
Speak up.
And I want every single detail.
Who was it that gave you this fancy magic wand?
Five seconds.
And now four.
Okay, okay, I'll tell you.
The truth is...
Get back inside!
That's it!
Don't you move, Mr. Magic Knight!
Take one step,
and the old lady dies.
Then you're gonna suffer a hundred times worse.
What does that mean?
Your little buddies won't do any more good than they did last time we fought.
No, you're obviously capable of defeating my men.
But this?
What the...
That's an earth magic spell by the name of Witch Hunter Claus.
Impressive, isn't it?
Then that's not all.
You're also trapped by a binding spell called Sheephorn Snag.
Wait a sec.
Don't I know you two?
That's right.
Crimson Goat and Silver Mole.
I never thought there'd be two traitors among us.
You guys have been feeding those bandits intel and magic items so they would go out and attack the villages and towns.
Haven't you?
That won't help you.
You can't break those bonds with mortal strength.
You're a damn disgrace to magic knights everywhere.
Ah, I remember.
You're that foreigner the Wizard King just promoted, aren't you?
Yami Sukuhiro.
I suspected he might be plotting something.
I guess this means I was correct.
In other words, when the Wizard King ordered the magic knights to guard these areas against bandit invasions,
it was nothing but a simple diversion, an attempt to narrow down where we'd strike next.
And you fell for it hook, line, and sinker.
I have to say, the whole situation's terribly amusing.
Excellent.
You two managed to capture him just in the nick of time.
I should have known you would have no problems with traps.
Stop standing around and go look for that treasure.
Oh, right.
Of course.
I'll have a look around the chief's house.
You, take me there.
Oh, okay.
Give me a hand, boys.
Yes, sir.
The magic knights are supposed to protect the people, not ransack their towns.
You're both monsters.
We'll be certain to fulfill our duty as magic knights by making the Wizard King aware that there's been a bandit incident in this area.
Don't go thinking you'll finish me off that easily.
I'll pay you back times a million.
Oh, I'm shaking in my shoe.
Anyway, we're done here.
How much longer can you keep that up?
You might as well surrender already.
Nah, it'll take a whole lot more than this.
I'm not done.
I'll break through.
Surely you've exhausted all your strength by now.
I'm just getting started.
I'll reach my limit and push past it.
Here and now.
Dracaena Formation.
Are you all right?
About time.
I got here as quickly as I could.
I realized we've been cut off.
And then, well, the only logical assumption was that the bandits must have appeared in Zokodane.
Uh-huh.
Guess I owe you one then.
In fact, I'll pay it off right now.
Ready for this?
Those punks are the traitors.
Gotenmo, you say?
Good to know.
Ah, William Vangeans.
I take it you're acting under the Wizard King's orders as well.
Then we'll just eliminate you and Yamae Sukuhiro in one fell swoop.
This again?
Now, attack of the horn!
Dark cloak like the slag!
I believe I said I'd pay you back a million times over, didn't I?
Um, please go easy on me if you don't mind.
Not bad at all, if you ask me.
Let me suggest something while I've gotten your attention.
I think you should consider coming over to our side.
Your side?
Sure, it's a lot of fun working with us.
My, how tempting.
Thank you, but I refuse.
I'm afraid I've sworn my absolute loyalty to the Wizard King.
Yes, of course you have.
Well, that's a terrible shame.
I figure that makes us about even.
You're right, it is a shame.
A shame that there were traitors hiding among the ranks of the Magic Knights.
Now then, one last thing.
Uh-huh.
Whoever that is, go get rid of him!
Aaaaaah!
I didn't intend to involve myself.
I mean, maybe a little bit.
Guess we're done.
Splendid job, you two.
Not only did you discover the Magic Knight traitors and capture them,
but you managed to round up the entire bandit group.
To be fair, we found the boss man unconscious up in a tree.
Haha, sometimes things just work out.
But, with my deepest sincerity,
you both did well.
Yami, William,
I'm so impressed with your performance.
I'd like to invite you to be captains of two new Magic Knight squads.
You're kidding!
You're asking us to lead our own squads?
I hope that you'll accept.
So, if both of us made the captain spot at once, I guess it's a tie.
That's true.
But the real race lies ahead.
Uh-huh.
I'll win.
Watch.
Keep dreaming.
I have every confidence in you.
So, Yami, what kind of squad would you like to form?
What kind, huh?
How do I put it?
Let me see.
How about a place for misfits to belong?
Where things like your rank and bloodline don't make any difference.
Where even hooligans are welcome.
You know, like the home you gave me.
I see.
An excellent idea.
As for the name, give me a second.
If I want lots of different people bringing all their colors to the table,
mixing them up till it's a big mess.
Hmm.
Oh.
If you put a bunch of different colors together, you'd get black.
So, I'll call us the Black, uh, the Black Bulls.
The Black Bulls it is.
Nice choice.
It suits you well.
And your team?
If I could.
I'd like to call mine the Golden Dawn.
Golden Dawn?
That's right.
And when it becomes the best of all, consider it my tribute to you.
True to its name, my squad will bring the shining gold of dawn to our world,
covering it with warmth and light.
Just as sunlight pierces even the darkest night,
we'll serve as a reminder to the people that Daybreak is sure to come.
You think really highly of yourself.
Such a beautiful sentiment.
I'm expecting great things.
Starting today, I hereby name you the official captain of the Golden Dawn.
Congratulations to you, William.
William, sir.
And Yami, from this moment on, you will be recognized as founder and leader of the Black Bulls.
Best of luck, Captain.
Let's do this, Goldie Guts.
And that's that.
Neat, huh?
Well, uh, a bunch of stuff did happen.
Um, what's the point you were trying to make again?
No, to never give up.
No matter how many times you may fall down.
Even if you're about to lose it all.
You can't quit on your dreams.
Always push past your limits.
So what if your rival outdid you this one time?
That's nothing.
If you lose 99 battles, just win the 100th.
Um, I'll keep that in mind.
Could have said it from the start, though.
Ow!
Sorry, there was a great story.
Please don't cross my head.
You know, the captain said some smart stuff in there.
There's no reason to be sad.
All right.
Time to work hard, catch up to Yuno, and leave him behind.
Hey, that reminds me.
Isn't it about time we got back the results from the Royal Knight Selection Exam?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
Woo!
Can't wait to see.
Bring it on, Mr. Owl.
I'm ready for you.
Damn.
That's the biggest owl I've ever heard.
Well, whoever you are, you can quit banging the door down already.
If you're looking for Captain Yami's black buzz, then you came to the...
Whoa, what just happened?
Hey, I recognize her.
That's Foigolian's sister!
What the hell says when you do this?
I'll be fine.
What's the winner?
Thank you.
I think you left some out.
We're on the mask Goldy Guts.
No, Baldy Guts Long John's Mustache Teacup.
Wait, no, damn it, I forgot.
Just call me William.
The selection exam results will be here any minute now.
I mean, not that it matters.
I totally made the cut, huh?
What do you mean?
I sound like I'm panicking.
Black Clover, page 87.
Formation of the Royal Knights.
I'm on fire, baby!